[{"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["floor"], "question": "Is there a floor in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "Is there a ladder in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "Is there a window in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [23, 24], "object_names": ["box", "box"], "question": "Is there a box in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "Is there a bench in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "Is there a shelf in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["computer"], "question": "Is there a computer in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [5, 11], "object_names": ["rail", "rail"], "question": "Is there a rail in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [45, 46, 48, 50, 51], "object_names": ["case", "case", "case", "case", "case"], "question": "Is there a case in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [17, 29], "object_names": ["chair", "chair"], "question": "Is there a chair in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a tissue box in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a bathtub in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a mask in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a toilet in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a tv in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a sack in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a glove in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a toaster in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a plunger in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Presence", "answers": ["No.", "No, there isn't."], "object_ids": [], "object_names": [], "question": "Is there a commode in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Presence_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "How many monitors are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [23, 24], "object_names": ["box", "box"], "question": "How many boxs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "How many laptops are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["floor"], "question": "How many floors are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [33], "object_names": ["step"], "question": "How many steps are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "How many bins are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "How many ladders are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "How many adhesive tapes are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [2, 6], "object_names": ["ceiling", "ceiling"], "question": "How many ceilings are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [42, 49], "object_names": ["bottle", "bottle"], "question": "How many bottles are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "How many shelfs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "How many mouses are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "How many papers are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["5"], "object_ids": [45, 46, 48, 50, 51], "object_names": ["case", "case", "case", "case", "case"], "question": "How many cases are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "How many lights are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "How many benchs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "How many stairss are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "How many desks are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [36, 37], "object_names": ["book", "book"], "question": "How many books are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_Quantity", "answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [1, 14], "object_names": ["wall", "wall"], "question": "How many walls are there in the room?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_Quantity_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["straight", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["vertically along one side of the wall", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["light blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["provides access to different levels"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["provides access to different levels"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is stairs. Its color is light blue. Its texture is wood grain patterns. Its material is wood, metal. Its size is medium. Its shape is straight. Its placement is vertically along one side of the wall. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["straight", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is stairs. Its color is light blue. Its texture is wood grain patterns. Its material is wood, metal. Its size is medium. Its placement is vertically along one side of the wall. Its function is provides access to different levels. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is stairs. Its color is light blue. Its texture is wood grain patterns. Its material is wood, metal. Its shape is straight. Its placement is vertically along one side of the wall. Its function is provides access to different levels. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wood, metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["stairs"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is stairs. Its color is light blue. Its texture is wood grain patterns. Its size is medium. Its shape is straight. Its placement is vertically along one side of the wall. Its function is provides access to different levels. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["shelf"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["mainly used for storage and can hold various items such as books, boxes, and small decorations"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["just right", "Medium"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its color is white. Its material is wood or similar materials. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on the ground. Its state is in good condition. Its function is mainly used for storage and can hold various items such as books, boxes, and small decorations. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its color is white. Its material is wood or similar materials. Its size is just right. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on the ground. Its function is mainly used for storage and can hold various items such as books, boxes, and small decorations. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wood or similar materials", "Wood"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its color is white. Its size is just right. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on the ground. Its state is in good condition. Its function is mainly used for storage and can hold various items such as books, boxes, and small decorations. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing vertically on the ground", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is shelf. Its color is white. Its material is wood or similar materials. Its size is just right. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is in good condition. Its function is mainly used for storage and can hold various items such as books, boxes, and small decorations. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["in good condition and well maintained"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rail"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sturdy", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "input_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its weight is sturdy. Its size is relatively thin. Its placement is installed vertically on the right side of the stairs. Its state is in good condition and well maintained. Its function is providing support for people going up and down the stairs. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["relatively thin", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its weight is sturdy. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is installed vertically on the right side of the stairs. Its state is in good condition and well maintained. Its function is providing support for people going up and down the stairs. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rail"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its weight is sturdy. Its size is relatively thin. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is installed vertically on the right side of the stairs. Its state is in good condition and well maintained. Its function is providing support for people going up and down the stairs. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["sturdy", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its size is relatively thin. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is installed vertically on the right side of the stairs. Its state is in good condition and well maintained. Its function is providing support for people going up and down the stairs. What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["plastic or paper", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["upright on a windowsill", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["plastic or paper", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is medium. Its shape is spherical, composed of multiple geometric shapes. Its placement is upright on a windowsill. Its function is decorative. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic or paper. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is medium. Its shape is spherical, composed of multiple geometric shapes. Its placement is upright on a windowsill. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["lightweight", "Light"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic or paper. Its size is medium. Its shape is spherical, composed of multiple geometric shapes. Its placement is upright on a windowsill. Its function is decorative. What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["upright on a windowsill", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic or paper. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is medium. Its shape is spherical, composed of multiple geometric shapes. Its function is decorative. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["allows natural light to enter the room and provides a view of the outside"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["glass"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["window"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["large"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is window. Its color is black. Its material is glass. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is center of the room. Its state is closed. Its function is allows natural light to enter the room and provides a view of the outside. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["center of the room", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is window. Its color is black. Its material is glass. Its size is large. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is allows natural light to enter the room and provides a view of the outside. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is window. Its material is glass. Its size is large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is center of the room. Its state is closed. Its function is allows natural light to enter the room and provides a view of the outside. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["glass"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["window"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is window. Its color is black. Its size is large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is center of the room. Its state is closed. Its function is allows natural light to enter the room and provides a view of the outside. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["dark", "Black"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["serves the purpose of safety, preventing falls from one level to another"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["spans the entire width of the room", "Large"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["streamlined, modern design with evenly spaced gaps between bars", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is dark. Its material is metal. Its size is spans the entire width of the room. Its placement is vertically positioned. Its function is serves the purpose of safety, preventing falls from one level to another. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is dark. Its size is spans the entire width of the room. Its shape is streamlined, modern design with evenly spaced gaps between bars. Its placement is vertically positioned. Its function is serves the purpose of safety, preventing falls from one level to another. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rail"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark. Its material is metal. Its size is spans the entire width of the room. Its shape is streamlined, modern design with evenly spaced gaps between bars. Its placement is vertically positioned. Its function is serves the purpose of safety, preventing falls from one level to another. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["spans the entire width of the room", "Large"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["rail"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is rail. Its color is dark. Its material is metal. Its shape is streamlined, modern design with evenly spaced gaps between bars. Its placement is vertically positioned. Its function is serves the purpose of safety, preventing falls from one level to another. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["off"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_25"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sleek"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_26"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["monitor"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "input_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_27"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is monitor. Its texture is sleek. Its size is standard. Its placement is vertically on a stand connected to the desk. Its state is off. Its function is displaying visual output from a connected device. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["monitor"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is sleek. Its size is standard. Its placement is vertically on a stand connected to the desk. Its state is off. Its function is displaying visual output from a connected device. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_25"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is monitor. Its color is black. Its texture is sleek. Its placement is vertically on a stand connected to the desk. Its state is off. Its function is displaying visual output from a connected device. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_26"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["off"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is monitor. Its color is black. Its texture is sleek. Its size is standard. Its placement is vertically on a stand connected to the desk. Its function is displaying visual output from a connected device. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_27"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sturdy metal frame", "Metal"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_28"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["set up vertically on a table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_29"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["printing 3D objects"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_30"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "input_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_31"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["printing 3D objects"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is sturdy metal frame. Its size is just the right size to comfortably sit on a desk. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is set up vertically on a table. Its state is in good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_28"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is sturdy metal frame. Its size is just the right size to comfortably sit on a desk. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is set up vertically on a table. Its function is printing 3D objects. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_29"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["set up vertically on a table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is sturdy metal frame. Its size is just the right size to comfortably sit on a desk. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is in good condition. Its function is printing 3D objects. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_30"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is sturdy metal frame. Its size is just the right size to comfortably sit on a desk. Its placement is set up vertically on a table. Its state is in good condition. Its function is printing 3D objects. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_31"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["ladder"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_32"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["neatly stacked with magazines"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_33"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["used for climbing or reaching higher places"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_34"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["warm brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_35"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["used for climbing or reaching higher places"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is ladder. Its color is warm brown. Its texture is rough. Its material is wood. Its size is tall. Its shape is straight. Its placement is leaning against the wall. Its state is neatly stacked with magazines. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_32"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["ladder"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is warm brown. Its texture is rough. Its material is wood. Its size is tall. Its shape is straight. Its placement is leaning against the wall. Its state is neatly stacked with magazines. Its function is used for climbing or reaching higher places. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_33"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["warm brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is ladder. Its texture is rough. Its material is wood. Its size is tall. Its shape is straight. Its placement is leaning against the wall. Its state is neatly stacked with magazines. Its function is used for climbing or reaching higher places. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_34"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["leaning against the wall", "Leaning"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["ladder"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is ladder. Its color is warm brown. Its texture is rough. Its material is wood. Its size is tall. Its shape is straight. Its state is neatly stacked with magazines. Its function is used for climbing or reaching higher places. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_35"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["provides comfort and functionality for the user"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_36"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["mesh, with armrests and backrest", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_37"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standard office chair shape", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_38"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_39"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its color is black. Its texture is mesh. Its material is mesh, with armrests and backrest. Its size is relatively smaller. Its shape is standard office chair shape. Its placement is in front of a desk. Its function is provides comfort and functionality for the user. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_36"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["mesh, with armrests and backrest", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its color is black. Its texture is mesh. Its size is relatively smaller. Its shape is standard office chair shape. Its placement is in front of a desk. Its state is in good condition. Its function is provides comfort and functionality for the user. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_37"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its texture is mesh. Its material is mesh, with armrests and backrest. Its size is relatively smaller. Its shape is standard office chair shape. Its placement is in front of a desk. Its state is in good condition. Its function is provides comfort and functionality for the user. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_38"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["in front of a desk", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its color is black. Its texture is mesh. Its material is mesh, with armrests and backrest. Its size is relatively smaller. Its shape is standard office chair shape. Its state is in good condition. Its function is provides comfort and functionality for the user. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_39"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_40"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["providing illumination"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_41"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["turned on"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_42"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["hanging vertically", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "input_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_43"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is light. Its texture is semi-transparent. Its material is plastic or glass. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is round. Its placement is hanging vertically. Its state is turned on. Its function is providing illumination. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_40"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["semi-transparent"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is light. Its color is white. Its material is plastic or glass. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is round. Its placement is hanging vertically. Its state is turned on. Its function is providing illumination. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_41"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is light. Its color is white. Its texture is semi-transparent. Its material is plastic or glass. Its size is relatively small. Its placement is hanging vertically. Its state is turned on. Its function is providing illumination. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_42"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["light"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is light. Its color is white. Its texture is semi-transparent. Its material is plastic or glass. Its shape is round. Its placement is hanging vertically. Its state is turned on. Its function is providing illumination. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_43"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_44"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["bench"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_45"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sits firmly on the floor"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_46"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["provides a comfortable seating area"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [20], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_47"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["sits firmly on the floor"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bench. Its color is light brown. Its texture is natural and warm. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is placed in the middle of the room. Its function is provides a comfortable seating area. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_44"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["natural and warm"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bench. Its color is light brown. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is placed in the middle of the room. Its state is sits firmly on the floor. Its function is provides a comfortable seating area. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_45"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wood"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bench. Its color is light brown. Its texture is natural and warm. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is placed in the middle of the room. Its state is sits firmly on the floor. Its function is provides a comfortable seating area. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_46"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [20], "object_names": ["bench"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bench. Its color is light brown. Its texture is natural and warm. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its placement is placed in the middle of the room. Its state is sits firmly on the floor. Its function is provides a comfortable seating area. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_47"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["laptop"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_48"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_49"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_50"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["allows users to access and use computer applications"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_51"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["glossy"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is laptop. Its color is black. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on the surface of a desk. Its function is allows users to access and use computer applications. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_48"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["lying flat on the surface of a desk", "Lying flat"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is laptop. Its color is black. Its texture is glossy. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its function is allows users to access and use computer applications. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_49"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is laptop. Its color is black. Its texture is glossy. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on the surface of a desk. Its function is allows users to access and use computer applications. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_50"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [22], "object_names": ["laptop"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is laptop. Its color is black. Its texture is glossy. Its size is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on the surface of a desk. Its function is allows users to access and use computer applications. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [22], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_51"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["beige with brown text and logos", "Brown"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_52"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_53"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sealed with black tape"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_54"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_55"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is box. Its color is beige with brown text and logos. Its material is cardboard with black tape. Its shape is rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms. Its placement is standing upright, leaning slightly to one side. Its state is sealed with black tape. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_52"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["sealed with black tape"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is box. Its color is beige with brown text and logos. Its material is cardboard with black tape. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms. Its placement is standing upright, leaning slightly to one side. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_53"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["cardboard with black tape", "Paper"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is box. Its color is beige with brown text and logos. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms. Its placement is standing upright, leaning slightly to one side. Its state is sealed with black tape. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_54"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [23], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is box. Its color is beige with brown text and logos. Its material is cardboard with black tape. Its size is medium. Its placement is standing upright, leaning slightly to one side. Its state is sealed with black tape. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_55"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_56"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["mainly white with a horizontal blue light strip on the front", "Blue"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_57"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["storage or transportation"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_58"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["box"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_59"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["storage or transportation"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is box. Its color is mainly white with a horizontal blue light strip on the front. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or metal. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on a table. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_56"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["upright on a table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is box. Its color is mainly white with a horizontal blue light strip on the front. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or metal. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is storage or transportation. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_57"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["mainly white with a horizontal blue light strip on the front", "Blue"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is box. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or metal. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on a table. Its state is closed. Its function is storage or transportation. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_58"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["box"], "object_ids": [24], "object_names": ["box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mainly white with a horizontal blue light strip on the front. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or metal. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on a table. Its state is closed. Its function is storage or transportation. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_59"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["cylindrical", "Medium"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [25], "input_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_60"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["organizes and stores pens, markers, and office supplies"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [25], "input_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_61"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [25], "input_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_62"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["flares out at the bottom", "Conical"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [25], "input_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_63"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or ceramic. Its size is cylindrical. Its shape is flares out at the bottom. Its placement is on the surface of a desk. Its state is contains various items. Its function is organizes and stores pens, markers, and office supplies. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [25], "output_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_60"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["contains various items"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or ceramic. Its size is cylindrical. Its shape is flares out at the bottom. Its placement is on the surface of a desk. Its function is organizes and stores pens, markers, and office supplies. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [25], "output_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_61"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["flares out at the bottom", "Conical"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or ceramic. Its size is cylindrical. Its placement is on the surface of a desk. Its state is contains various items. Its function is organizes and stores pens, markers, and office supplies. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [25], "output_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_62"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["organizes and stores pens, markers, and office supplies"], "object_ids": [25], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic or ceramic. Its size is cylindrical. Its shape is flares out at the bottom. Its placement is on the surface of a desk. Its state is contains various items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [25], "output_bboxes": [[0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_63"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["pink"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [26], "input_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_64"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [26], "input_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_65"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [26], "input_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_66"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["upright on the left side of the table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [26], "input_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_67"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["used for disposing trash"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is pink. Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the left side of the table. Its state is slightly ajar. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [26], "output_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_64"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is pink. Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the left side of the table. Its function is used for disposing trash. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [26], "output_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_65"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["upright on the left side of the table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is pink. Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is slightly ajar. Its function is used for disposing trash. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [26], "output_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_66"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [26], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is pink. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the left side of the table. Its state is slightly ajar. Its function is used for disposing trash. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [26], "output_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_67"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_68"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["desk"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_69"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_70"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["in the center of the room", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_71"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["unoccupied"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is desk. Its color is light brown. Its material is wooden. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is in the center of the room. Its function is provides ample space for various items. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_68"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is desk. Its color is light brown. Its material is wooden. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is in the center of the room. Its state is unoccupied. Its function is provides ample space for various items. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_69"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is desk. Its color is light brown. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is in the center of the room. Its state is unoccupied. Its function is provides ample space for various items. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_70"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["provides ample space for various items"], "object_ids": [27], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is desk. Its color is light brown. Its material is wooden. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is in the center of the room. Its state is unoccupied. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [27], "output_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_71"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["clear", "Transparent"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_72"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_73"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["holds various small objects"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_74"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_75"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clear. Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is slightly ajar. Its function is holds various small objects. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_72"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["holds various small objects"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clear. Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is slightly ajar. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_73"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["clear", "Transparent"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is slightly ajar. Its function is holds various small objects. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_74"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clear. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is slightly ajar. Its function is holds various small objects. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [28], "output_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_75"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["plastic or composite materials", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_76"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_77"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_78"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["chair"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_79"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its color is white. Its material is plastic or composite materials. Its shape is gracefully curved backrest and sleek seat. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is great condition. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_76"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its color is white. Its material is plastic or composite materials. Its size is medium. Its shape is gracefully curved backrest and sleek seat. Its placement is standing upright. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_77"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its material is plastic or composite materials. Its size is medium. Its shape is gracefully curved backrest and sleek seat. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is great condition. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_78"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["gracefully curved backrest and sleek seat", "Irregular"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is chair. Its color is white. Its material is plastic or composite materials. Its size is medium. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is great condition. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_79"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "input_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_80"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "input_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_81"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["stores items"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "input_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_82"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "input_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_83"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["transparent"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat. Its state is closed. Its function is stores items. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_80"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its placement is lying flat. Its state is closed. Its function is stores items. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_81"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat. Its state is closed. Its function is stores items. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_82"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat. Its function is stores items. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_83"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["stable support", "Medium"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "input_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_84"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["provides stable support"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "input_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_85"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["sturdy"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "input_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_86"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["triangular"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "input_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_87"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["provides stable support"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is sturdy. Its material is wooden. Its size is stable support. Its shape is triangular. Its placement is evenly spread out on the ground. Its state is empty. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_84"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is sturdy. Its size is stable support. Its shape is triangular. Its placement is evenly spread out on the ground. Its state is empty. Its function is provides stable support. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_85"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["stable support", "Medium"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is sturdy. Its material is wooden. Its shape is triangular. Its placement is evenly spread out on the ground. Its state is empty. Its function is provides stable support. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_86"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is sturdy. Its material is wooden. Its size is stable support. Its shape is triangular. Its placement is evenly spread out on the ground. Its state is empty. Its function is provides stable support. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_87"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["placed in the center of a room", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "input_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_88"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "input_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_89"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "input_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_90"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["providing a space for work or study"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "input_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_91"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is wooden. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is placed in the center of a room. Its state is in good condition. Its function is providing a space for work or study. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_88"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wooden. Its size is medium. Its placement is placed in the center of a room. Its state is in good condition. Its function is providing a space for work or study. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_89"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wooden. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is placed in the center of a room. Its function is providing a space for work or study. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_90"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["providing a space for work or study"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wooden. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is placed in the center of a room. Its state is in good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes": [[-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_91"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_92"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_93"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["provides information or entertainment"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_94"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["book"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_95"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing vertically on a wooden bookshelf", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is book. Its color is mostly white with some black text and designs. Its material is hardcover. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is great condition. Its function is provides information or entertainment. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_92"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["mostly white with some black text and designs", "Black"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is book. Its material is hardcover. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on a wooden bookshelf. Its state is great condition. Its function is provides information or entertainment. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_93"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["provides information or entertainment"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is book. Its color is mostly white with some black text and designs. Its material is hardcover. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on a wooden bookshelf. Its state is great condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_94"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["hardcover", "Paper"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is book. Its color is mostly white with some black text and designs. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically on a wooden bookshelf. Its state is great condition. Its function is provides information or entertainment. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_95"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "input_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_96"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "input_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_97"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "input_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_98"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "input_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_99"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is book. Its color is white. Its material is paper. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is good condition. Its function is ordinary book for reading. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_96"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is book. Its color is white. Its material is paper. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is ordinary book for reading. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_97"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["book"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is paper. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is good condition. Its function is ordinary book for reading. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_98"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["book"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is book. Its material is paper. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is good condition. Its function is ordinary book for reading. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_99"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["suitable for climbing or placing items on higher surfaces"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_100"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["leaning", "Irregular"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_101"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["against a wall", "Leaning"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_102"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["not fully extended, top step slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_103"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["leaning", "Irregular"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is rough. Its material is wooden. Its size is 3 steps with the top one being the smallest. Its placement is against a wall. Its state is not fully extended, top step slightly tilted. Its function is suitable for climbing or placing items on higher surfaces. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_100"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is rough. Its size is 3 steps with the top one being the smallest. Its shape is leaning. Its placement is against a wall. Its state is not fully extended, top step slightly tilted. Its function is suitable for climbing or placing items on higher surfaces. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_101"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rough"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is wooden. Its size is 3 steps with the top one being the smallest. Its shape is leaning. Its placement is against a wall. Its state is not fully extended, top step slightly tilted. Its function is suitable for climbing or placing items on higher surfaces. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_102"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["not fully extended, top step slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is rough. Its material is wooden. Its size is 3 steps with the top one being the smallest. Its shape is leaning. Its placement is against a wall. Its function is suitable for climbing or placing items on higher surfaces. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes": [[1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_103"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["A4", "Medium"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_104"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["paper"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_105"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["lying flat"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_106"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["for writing or printing"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_107"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["for writing or printing"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is paper. Its color is white. Its size is A4. Its shape is rectangular with slightly curved bottom. Its placement is lying flat. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_104"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["lying flat"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is paper. Its color is white. Its size is A4. Its shape is rectangular with slightly curved bottom. Its function is for writing or printing. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_105"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["A4", "Medium"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is paper. Its color is white. Its shape is rectangular with slightly curved bottom. Its placement is lying flat. Its function is for writing or printing. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_106"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is paper. Its size is A4. Its shape is rectangular with slightly curved bottom. Its placement is lying flat. Its function is for writing or printing. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_107"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["on a round black mouse pad, on a wooden surface", "Lying flat"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_108"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_109"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["mouse"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_110"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_111"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is mouse. Its color is black. Its texture is sleek. Its size is small. Its shape is oval. Its placement is on a round black mouse pad, on a wooden surface. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_108"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["small"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is mouse. Its color is black. Its texture is sleek. Its material is plastic. Its shape is oval. Its placement is on a round black mouse pad, on a wooden surface. What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_109"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is mouse. Its texture is sleek. Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its shape is oval. Its placement is on a round black mouse pad, on a wooden surface. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_110"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["mouse"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["mouse"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is sleek. Its material is plastic. Its size is small. Its shape is oval. Its placement is on a round black mouse pad, on a wooden surface. What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_111"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["glass"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "input_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_112"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["bottle"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "input_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_113"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["cylinder", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "input_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_114"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["used for holding water or drinks"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "input_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_115"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing upright on a shelf", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is predominantly white. Its material is glass. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is cylinder. Its state is in good condition. Its function is used for holding water or drinks. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_112"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is predominantly white. Its material is glass. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is cylinder. Its placement is standing upright on a shelf. Its function is used for holding water or drinks. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_113"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["used for holding water or drinks"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is predominantly white. Its material is glass. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is cylinder. Its placement is standing upright on a shelf. Its state is in good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_114"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["cylinder", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is predominantly white. Its material is glass. Its size is medium-sized. Its placement is standing upright on a shelf. Its state is in good condition. Its function is used for holding water or drinks. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_115"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "input_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_116"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "input_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_117"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "input_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_118"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["used for sealing or binding purposes"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "input_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_119"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["used for sealing or binding purposes"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is adhesive tape. Its color is white. Its size is 2 inches in length. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is neatly placed on a cardboard box. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_116"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is adhesive tape. Its color is white. Its size is 2 inches in length. Its placement is neatly placed on a cardboard box. Its state is good condition. Its function is used for sealing or binding purposes. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_117"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["neatly placed on a cardboard box", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is adhesive tape. Its color is white. Its size is 2 inches in length. Its shape is cylindrical. Its state is good condition. Its function is used for sealing or binding purposes. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_118"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is adhesive tape. Its size is 2 inches in length. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is neatly placed on a cardboard box. Its state is good condition. Its function is used for sealing or binding purposes. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_119"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["wood"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_120"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_121"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["holding household items"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_122"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_123"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is next to a wall. Its function is holding household items. What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_120"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["blue"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is next to a wall. Its function is holding household items. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_121"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its placement is next to a wall. Its function is holding household items. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_122"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["wood"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is smooth. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is next to a wall. Its function is holding household items. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_123"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_124"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_125"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_126"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["bottle"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "What is type of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_127"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is cylindrical. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is standing upright. Its function is storing and pouring liquids. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_124"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is cylindrical. Its shape is cylindrical. Its state is closed. Its function is storing and pouring liquids. What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_125"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is cylindrical. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. Its function is storing and pouring liquids. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_126"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["bottle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its type is bottle. Its color is white. Its size is cylindrical. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. Its function is storing and pouring liquids. What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_127"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["paper"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [53], "input_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_128"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [53], "input_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_129"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [53], "input_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_130"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single0", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [53], "input_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Attribute_single0_131"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is paper. Its size is average. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. Its function is organizing and storing documents. What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [53], "output_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_128"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is paper. Its size is average. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its function is organizing and storing documents. What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [53], "output_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_129"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is paper. Its size is average. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. Its function is organizing and storing documents. What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [53], "output_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_130"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Attribute_single1", "answers": ["organizing and storing documents"], "object_ids": [53], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is paper. Its size is average. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [53], "output_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Attribute_single1_131"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "select the box that is  lying on the bench. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "select the box that is  on the bench. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["plastic or metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "select the box that is  on the bench. What is material of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["plastic or composite materials", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["chair", "shelf"], "question": "facing the front of the shelf, choose the chair that is behind it. What is material of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "select the box that is  lying on the bench. What is size of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "select the box that is  lying on the bench. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["upright on a table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "select the box that is  on the bench. What is placement of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["streamlined, modern design with evenly spaced gaps between bars", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [11, 9], "object_names": ["rail", "window"], "question": "looking at the front of the window, choose the rail that is behind it. What is shape of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright, leaning slightly to one side", "Leaning"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "looking at the front of the laptop, pick the box that is on the right side of the laptop. What is placement of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [49, 43], "object_names": ["bottle", "adhesive tape"], "question": "find the bottle that is under the adhesive. What is shape of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "facing the front of the laptop, select the box that is on the right side of it. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["sealed with black tape"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "looking at the front of the laptop, pick the box that is to the right of the laptop. What is state of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["mesh"], "object_ids": [17, 40], "object_names": ["chair", "mouse"], "question": "looking at the front of the mouse, pick the chair that is behind the mouse. What is texture of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "facing the front of the step, choose the rail that is on the right side of it. What is shape of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["chair", "shelf"], "question": "looking at the front of the shelf, select the chair that is behind it. What is state of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["installed vertically on the right side of the stairs", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "looking at the front of the step, select the rail that is to the right of it. What is placement of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["beige with brown text and logos", "Brown"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "facing the front of the laptop, select the box that is on the right of it. What is color of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [49, 43], "object_names": ["bottle", "adhesive tape"], "question": "find the bottle that is under the adhesive. What is placement of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [49, 43], "object_names": ["bottle", "adhesive tape"], "question": "find the bottle that is beneath the adhesive. What is placement of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["mesh, with armrests and backrest", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [17, 3], "object_names": ["chair", "stairs"], "question": "the chair that is close to the stairs. What is material of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [29, 3], "object_names": ["chair", "stairs"], "question": "choose the chair that is far away from the stairs. What is state of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["chair", "shelf"], "question": "facing the front of the shelf, choose the chair that is on the back of it. What is state of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [5, 3], "object_names": ["rail", "stairs"], "question": "find the rail that is near the stairs. What is shape of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["gracefully curved backrest and sleek seat", "Irregular"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["chair", "shelf"], "question": "facing the front of the shelf, choose the chair that is behind it. What is shape of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [5, 3], "object_names": ["rail", "stairs"], "question": "find the rail that is close to the stairs. What is shape of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["in good condition and well maintained"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "looking at the front of the step, select the rail that is on the right side of it. What is state of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_25"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["relatively smaller", "Small"], "object_ids": [17, 3], "object_names": ["chair", "stairs"], "question": "the chair that is close to the stairs. What is size of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_26"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "select the box that is  lying on the bench. What is state of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_27"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["chair", "shelf"], "question": "facing the front of the shelf, choose the chair that is behind it. What is placement of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_28"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [24, 3], "object_names": ["box", "stairs"], "question": "select the box that is near the stairs. What is state of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_29"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [24, 4], "object_names": ["box", "shelf"], "question": "the box that is close to the shelf. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_30"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "facing the front of the laptop, select the box that is to the right of it. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_31"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["upright on a table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [24, 3], "object_names": ["box", "stairs"], "question": "select the box that is near the stairs. What is placement of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_32"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [29, 3], "object_names": ["chair", "stairs"], "question": "choose the chair that is far from the stairs. What is size of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_33"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "facing the front of the step, choose the rail that is on the right side of it. What is color of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_34"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [49, 4], "object_names": ["bottle", "shelf"], "question": "select the bottle that is close to the shelf. What is shape of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_35"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["relatively thin", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "looking at the front of the step, select the rail that is to the right of it. What is size of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_36"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [49, 4], "object_names": ["bottle", "shelf"], "question": "select the bottle that is close to the shelf. What is shape of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_37"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standard office chair shape", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [17, 40], "object_names": ["chair", "mouse"], "question": "looking at the front of the mouse, pick the chair that is behind the mouse. What is shape of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_38"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [23, 3], "object_names": ["box", "stairs"], "question": "find the box that is far from the stairs. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_39"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [29, 12], "object_names": ["chair", "monitor"], "question": "choose the chair that is next to the monitor. What is color of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_40"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["sturdy", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5, 12], "object_names": ["rail", "monitor"], "question": "choose the rail that is near the monitor. What is weight of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_41"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["in front of a desk", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [17, 9], "object_names": ["chair", "window"], "question": "select the chair that is close to the window. What is placement of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_42"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "looking at the front of the step, select the rail that is on the right of it. What is material of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_43"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [24, 4], "object_names": ["box", "shelf"], "question": "the box that is near the shelf. What is texture of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_44"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["mesh, with armrests and backrest", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [17, 9], "object_names": ["chair", "window"], "question": "select the chair that is close to the window. What is material of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_45"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright on a shelf", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [42, 3], "object_names": ["bottle", "stairs"], "question": "find the bottle that is far away from the stairs. What is placement of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_46"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [49, 16], "object_names": ["bottle", "ladder"], "question": "choose the bottle that is near the ladder. What is placement of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_47"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [29, 9], "object_names": ["chair", "window"], "question": "choose the chair that is far away from the window. What is placement of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_48"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["in good condition and well maintained"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "facing the front of the step, choose the rail that is on the right side of it. What is state of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_49"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [29, 9], "object_names": ["chair", "window"], "question": "choose the chair that is far away from the window. What is size of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_50"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [29, 12], "object_names": ["chair", "monitor"], "question": "choose the chair that is next to the monitor. What is size of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_51"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [42, 12], "object_names": ["bottle", "monitor"], "question": "select the bottle that is far from the monitor. What is state of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_52"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["plastic or composite materials", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [29, 20], "object_names": ["chair", "bench"], "question": "choose the chair that is far from the bench. What is material of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_53"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["cylinder", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [42, 12], "object_names": ["bottle", "monitor"], "question": "select the bottle that is far from the monitor. What is shape of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_54"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["relatively smaller", "Small"], "object_ids": [17, 16], "object_names": ["chair", "ladder"], "question": "find the chair that is far away from the ladder. What is size of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_55"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["installed vertically on the right side of the stairs", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [5, 22], "object_names": ["rail", "laptop"], "question": "find the rail that is far away from the laptop. What is placement of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_56"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["installed vertically on the right side of the stairs", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [5, 27], "object_names": ["rail", "desk"], "question": "choose the rail that is close to the desk. What is placement of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_57"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["upright on a table", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "find the box that is close to the bench. What is placement of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_58"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "facing the front of the laptop, select the box that is to the right of it. What is size of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_59"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["dark", "Black"], "object_ids": [11, 12], "object_names": ["rail", "monitor"], "question": "the rail that is far away from the monitor. What is color of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_60"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["metal"], "object_ids": [11, 27], "object_names": ["rail", "desk"], "question": "the rail that is far away from the desk. What is material of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_61"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [29, 22], "object_names": ["chair", "laptop"], "question": "the chair that is far from the laptop. What is state of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_62"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [24, 20], "object_names": ["box", "bench"], "question": "find the box that is close to the bench. What is texture of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_63"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["relatively thin", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5, 27], "object_names": ["rail", "desk"], "question": "choose the rail that is close to the desk. What is size of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_64"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [49, 43], "object_names": ["bottle", "adhesive tape"], "question": "find the bottle that is beneath the adhesive. What is material of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_65"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["chair", "shelf"], "question": "select the chair that is far from the shelf. What is state of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_66"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["gracefully curved backrest and sleek seat", "Irregular"], "object_ids": [29, 3], "object_names": ["chair", "stairs"], "question": "choose the chair that is far away from the stairs. What is shape of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_67"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [29, 12], "object_names": ["chair", "monitor"], "question": "choose the chair that is next to the monitor. What is size of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_68"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular with slightly tapered tops and bottoms", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "facing the front of the laptop, select the box that is on the right side of it. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_69"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["sealed with black tape"], "object_ids": [23, 22], "object_names": ["box", "laptop"], "question": "looking at the front of the laptop, pick the box that is to the right of the laptop. What is state of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [23], "output_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_70"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["cylindrical", "Medium"], "object_ids": [49, 12], "object_names": ["bottle", "monitor"], "question": "choose the bottle that is close to the monitor. What is size of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_71"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "looking at the front of the step, select the rail that is on the right side of it. What is shape of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_72"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["black"], "object_ids": [5, 22], "object_names": ["rail", "laptop"], "question": "find the rail that is far away from the laptop. What is color of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_73"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["sturdy", "Medium"], "object_ids": [5, 33], "object_names": ["rail", "step"], "question": "find the rail that is close to the step. What is weight of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_74"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [49, 43], "object_names": ["bottle", "adhesive tape"], "question": "find the bottle that is under the adhesive. What is placement of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_75"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [24, 32], "object_names": ["box", "computer"], "question": "select the box that is near the computer. What is size of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_76"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [24, 32], "object_names": ["box", "computer"], "question": "select the box that is near the computer. What is shape of the box ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [24], "output_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_77"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["mesh"], "object_ids": [17, 16], "object_names": ["chair", "ladder"], "question": "find the chair that is far from the ladder. What is texture of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_78"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["medium"], "object_ids": [29, 16], "object_names": ["chair", "ladder"], "question": "the chair that is near the ladder. What is size of the chair ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_79"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [49, 16], "object_names": ["bottle", "ladder"], "question": "choose the bottle that is near the ladder. What is material of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_80"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["white"], "object_ids": [49, 27], "object_names": ["bottle", "desk"], "question": "the bottle that is near the desk. What is color of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_81"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["plastic"], "object_ids": [49, 12], "object_names": ["bottle", "monitor"], "question": "choose the bottle that is near the monitor. What is material of the bottle ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_82"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Space", "answers": ["vertically positioned", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [11, 9], "object_names": ["rail", "window"], "question": "choose the rail that is near the window. What is placement of the rail ?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": null, "input_bboxes": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes": [[-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "ID": "QA_Relation_Space_83"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the window and the desk are both Furniture"], "object_ids": [9, 27], "object_names": ["window", "desk"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the box and the object are both Store and organize supplies"], "object_ids": [24, 30], "object_names": ["box", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24, 30], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the paper and the adhesive tape are both Study and office supplies"], "object_ids": [39, 43], "object_names": ["paper", "adhesive tape"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39, 43], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the bottle and the bottle are both Kitchenware and dining utensil"], "object_ids": [49, 42], "object_names": ["bottle", "bottle"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49, 42], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the monitor and the laptop are both Electronic products"], "object_ids": [12, 22], "object_names": ["monitor", "laptop"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [12, 22], "input_bboxes": [[-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the box is Store and organize supplies and the bottle is Kitchenware and dining utensil"], "object_ids": [23, 42], "object_names": ["box", "bottle"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23, 42], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the desk is Furniture and the mouse is Electronic products"], "object_ids": [27, 40], "object_names": ["desk", "mouse"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27, 40], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the mouse is Electronic products and the stairs is Furniture"], "object_ids": [40, 3], "object_names": ["mouse", "stairs"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40, 3], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the bottle is Kitchenware and dining utensil and the laptop is Electronic products"], "object_ids": [49, 22], "object_names": ["bottle", "laptop"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49, 22], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the bottle is Kitchenware and dining utensil and the adhesive tape is Study and office supplies"], "object_ids": [49, 43], "object_names": ["bottle", "adhesive tape"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49, 43], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the stairs and the box are both Blue"], "object_ids": [3, 24], "object_names": ["stairs", "box"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 24], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the laptop and the window are both Black"], "object_ids": [22, 9], "object_names": ["laptop", "window"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22, 9], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the chair and the paper are both White"], "object_ids": [29, 39], "object_names": ["chair", "paper"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29, 39], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the ladder and the object are both Brown"], "object_ids": [16, 34], "object_names": ["ladder", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 34], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the object are both Transparent"], "object_ids": [30, 28], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [30, 28], "input_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the mouse is Black and the adhesive tape is White"], "object_ids": [40, 43], "object_names": ["mouse", "adhesive tape"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40, 43], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the box is Blue and the box is Brown"], "object_ids": [24, 23], "object_names": ["box", "box"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24, 23], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the book is Black and the object is Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 34], "object_names": ["book", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36, 34], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the stairs is Blue and the object is Transparent"], "object_ids": [3, 30], "object_names": ["stairs", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 30], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the paper is White and the bench is Brown"], "object_ids": [39, 20], "object_names": ["paper", "bench"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39, 20], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the desk are both Wood"], "object_ids": [34, 27], "object_names": ["object", "desk"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [34, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the box and the rail are both Metal"], "object_ids": [24, 5], "object_names": ["box", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24, 5], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the chair and the mouse are both Plastic"], "object_ids": [29, 40], "object_names": ["chair", "mouse"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29, 40], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the window and the bottle are both Glass"], "object_ids": [9, 42], "object_names": ["window", "bottle"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 42], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the box are both Paper"], "object_ids": [53, 23], "object_names": ["object", "box"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [53, 23], "input_bboxes": [[-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the rail is Metal and the bottle is Plastic"], "object_ids": [5, 49], "object_names": ["rail", "bottle"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 49], "input_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_25"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the box is Paper and the rail is Metal"], "object_ids": [23, 5], "object_names": ["box", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23, 5], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_26"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the rail is Metal and the bottle is Glass"], "object_ids": [5, 42], "object_names": ["rail", "bottle"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 42], "input_bboxes": [[-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_27"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the bench is Wood and the box is Metal"], "object_ids": [20, 24], "object_names": ["bench", "box"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [20, 24], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_28"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the bottle is Plastic and the rail is Metal"], "object_ids": [49, 11], "object_names": ["bottle", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49, 11], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_29"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the bench and the book are both Rectangular"], "object_ids": [20, 37], "object_names": ["bench", "book"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [20, 37], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_30"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the mouse and the light are both Circular"], "object_ids": [40, 18], "object_names": ["mouse", "light"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40, 18], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_31"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the bottle and the adhesive tape are both Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [49, 43], "object_names": ["bottle", "adhesive tape"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [49, 43], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_32"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the box and the paper are both Cuboid"], "object_ids": [23, 39], "object_names": ["box", "paper"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23, 39], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_33"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the object and the object are both Irregular"], "object_ids": [8, 38], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [8, 38], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_34"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the mouse is Circular and the object is Irregular"], "object_ids": [40, 38], "object_names": ["mouse", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40, 38], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_35"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the box is Cuboid and the chair is Irregular"], "object_ids": [23, 29], "object_names": ["box", "chair"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23, 29], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_36"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Rectangular and the mouse is Circular"], "object_ids": [26, 40], "object_names": ["object", "mouse"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [26, 40], "input_bboxes": [[-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_37"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the bottle is Cylindrical and the rail is Rectangular"], "object_ids": [42, 11], "object_names": ["bottle", "rail"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [42, 11], "input_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_38"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the box is Cuboid and the light is Circular"], "object_ids": [23, 18], "object_names": ["box", "light"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23, 18], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_39"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [37, 55], "object_names": [37, 55], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [37, 55], "input_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_40"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [42, 57], "object_names": [42, 57], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [42, 57], "input_bboxes": [[-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_41"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [39, 50], "object_names": [39, 50], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39, 50], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_42"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [18, 20], "object_names": [18, 20], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [18, 20], "input_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_43"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [15, 31], "object_names": [15, 31], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [15, 31], "input_bboxes": [[-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_44"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [43, 17], "object_names": [43, 17], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [43, 17], "input_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_45"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [9, 33], "object_names": [9, 33], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 33], "input_bboxes": [[-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_46"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [4, 13], "object_names": [4, 13], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [4, 13], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_47"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [51, 32], "object_names": [51, 32], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [51, 32], "input_bboxes": [[-2.624072497980592, 0.6102935964298466, 0.06598355939117019, 0.34380276426877165, 0.37878982523741744, 0.07804945239091585, -1.2701413521302949, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_48"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [48, 5], "object_names": [48, 5], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [48, 5], "input_bboxes": [[-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_49"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [24, 53], "object_names": [24, 53], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [24, 53], "input_bboxes": [[-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_50"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No"], "object_ids": [34, 12], "object_names": [34, 12], "question": "Are these two objects similar in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [34, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_51"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": [0], "object_ids": [28], "object_names": [28], "question": "How many objects are similar to this object in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [28], "input_bboxes": [[0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": [1], "object_ids": [55, 41], "object_names": [55, 41], "question": "How many objects are similar to this object in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "input_bboxes": [[-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": [3], "object_ids": [29, 9, 16, 35], "object_names": [29, 9, 16, 35], "question": "How many objects are similar to this object in size?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the stairs and the object are both Standing upright"], "object_ids": [3, 26], "object_names": ["stairs", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 26], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_52"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the box and the object are both Leaning"], "object_ids": [23, 44], "object_names": ["box", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [23, 44], "input_bboxes": [[-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_53"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["Yes, the mouse and the object are both Lying flat"], "object_ids": [40, 30], "object_names": ["mouse", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40, 30], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_54"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the stairs is Standing upright and the ladder is Leaning"], "object_ids": [3, 16], "object_names": ["stairs", "ladder"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 16], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_55"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the laptop is Lying flat and the object is Leaning"], "object_ids": [22, 38], "object_names": ["laptop", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22, 38], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_56"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute0", "answers": ["No, the object is Leaning and the adhesive tape is Standing upright"], "object_ids": [44, 43], "object_names": ["object", "adhesive tape"], "question": "Are these two objects same in placement? Why?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [44, 43], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute0_57"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": ["21"], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 15, 17, 18, 24, 26, 27, 28, 29, 35, 36, 37, 42, 43, 49, 53], "object_names": ["stairs", "shelf", "rail", "object", "window", "rail", "monitor", "object", "chair", "light", "box", "object", "desk", "object", "chair", "object", "book", "book", "bottle", "adhesive tape", "bottle", "object"], "question": "How many other objects are the same as this object in the placement?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": ["3"], "object_ids": [16, 23, 38, 44], "object_names": ["ladder", "box", "object", "object"], "question": "How many other objects are the same as this object in the placement?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Attribute1", "answers": ["6"], "object_ids": [20, 22, 25, 30, 34, 39, 40], "object_names": ["bench", "laptop", "object", "object", "object", "paper", "mouse"], "question": "How many other objects are the same as this object in the placement?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "input_bboxes": [[-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Attribute1_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["computer displays visual output from monitor."], "object_ids": [32, 12], "object_names": ["computer", "monitor"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [32, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The desk is used for work and study activities on the laptop."], "object_ids": [27, 22], "object_names": ["desk", "laptop"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27, 22], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [27, 22], "object_names": ["desk", "laptop"], "question": "In the dining region, this laptop and X have relationship in their function:The X is used for work and study activities on the laptop. What is the shape of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["provides ample space for various items"], "object_ids": [27, 22], "object_names": ["desk", "laptop"], "question": "In the dining region, this laptop and X have relationship in their function:The X is used for work and study activities on the laptop. What is the function of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [22], "input_bboxes": [[-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["chair is used to sit and work or study at desk."], "object_ids": [17, 27], "object_names": ["chair", "desk"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [17, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["in front of a desk", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [17, 27], "object_names": ["chair", "desk"], "question": "In the dining region, this desk and X have relationship in their function:X is used to sit and work or study at desk. What is the placement of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["chair"], "object_ids": [17, 27], "object_names": ["chair", "desk"], "question": "In the dining region, this desk and X have relationship in their function:X is used to sit and work or study at desk. What is the type of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The chair is used for sitting at the desk to perform various tasks, such as writing or using a laptop."], "object_ids": [29, 27], "object_names": ["chair", "desk"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [29, 27], "input_bboxes": [[0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["gracefully curved backrest and sleek seat", "Irregular"], "object_ids": [29, 27], "object_names": ["chair", "desk"], "question": "In the dining region, this desk and X have relationship in their function:The X is used for sitting at the desk to perform various tasks, such as writing or using a laptop. What is the shape of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [29, 27], "object_names": ["chair", "desk"], "question": "In the dining region, this desk and X have relationship in their function:The X is used for sitting at the desk to perform various tasks, such as writing or using a laptop. What is the state of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The mouse is an auxiliary device that helps to interact with the computer."], "object_ids": [40, 32], "object_names": ["mouse", "computer"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [40, 32], "input_bboxes": [[-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["oval", "Circular"], "object_ids": [40, 32], "object_names": ["mouse", "computer"], "question": "In the dining region, this computer and X have relationship in their function:The X is an auxiliary device that helps to interact with the computer. What is the shape of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "input_bboxes": [[-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["on a round black mouse pad, on a wooden surface", "Lying flat"], "object_ids": [40, 32], "object_names": ["mouse", "computer"], "question": "In the dining region, this computer and X have relationship in their function:The X is an auxiliary device that helps to interact with the computer. What is the placement of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "input_bboxes": [[-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["desk is often placed on paper for writing or reading."], "object_ids": [27, 39], "object_names": ["desk", "paper"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [27, 39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [27, 39], "object_names": ["desk", "paper"], "question": "In the dining region, this paper and X have relationship in their function:X is often placed on paper for writing or reading. What is the shape of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["in the center of the room", "Standing upright"], "object_ids": [27, 39], "object_names": ["desk", "paper"], "question": "In the dining region, this paper and X have relationship in their function:X is often placed on paper for writing or reading. What is the placement of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["paper can be used to stick adhesive tape onto a surface."], "object_ids": [43, 39], "object_names": ["adhesive tape", "paper"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [43, 39], "input_bboxes": [[-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["2 inches in length", "Small"], "object_ids": [43, 39], "object_names": ["adhesive tape", "paper"], "question": "In the dining region, this paper and X have relationship in their function:paper can be used to stick X onto a surface. What is the size of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["cylindrical"], "object_ids": [43, 39], "object_names": ["adhesive tape", "paper"], "question": "In the dining region, this paper and X have relationship in their function:paper can be used to stick X onto a surface. What is the shape of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "input_bboxes": [[-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The cup is placed on the desk and is used for drinking beverages during work or study."], "object_ids": [41, 27], "object_names": ["cup", "desk"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [41, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The cup can be used to hold writing tools or for drinking, and is usually placed on the desk for easy access."], "object_ids": [58, 27], "object_names": ["cup", "desk"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [58, 27], "input_bboxes": [[-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["A bin is a place where paper is discarded after use."], "object_ids": [31, 39], "object_names": ["bin", "paper"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [31, 39], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["These pieces of furniture belong to the category of study room furniture, providing a comfortable and practical area for reading, writing, and working."], "object_ids": [4, 17, 18, 9, 20, 22, 27, 29, 32, 39, 40, 43, 12], "object_names": ["shelf", "chair", "light", "window", "bench", "laptop", "desk", "chair", "computer", "paper", "mouse", "adhesive tape", "monitor"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 13 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [4, 17, 18, 9, 20, 22, 27, 29, 32, 39, 40, 43, 12], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["These are drinking utensils, used to hold beverages while studying or working for long periods in the study area."], "object_ids": [41, 58, 49, 42], "object_names": ["cup", "cup", "bottle", "bottle"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 4 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [41, 58, 49, 42], "input_bboxes": [[-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["These items are part of the lighting and power supply curriculum, providing illumination and electrical support for workspaces."], "object_ids": [18, 52], "object_names": ["light", "object"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 2 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [18, 52], "input_bboxes": [[0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["These are waste management items, with <bin_31> used for disposing of items like <paper_39>."], "object_ids": [31, 39], "object_names": ["bin", "paper"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 2 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [31, 39], "input_bboxes": [[-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["This is used to organize and manage space, in order to achieve the goal of making the room cleaner and tidier."], "object_ids": [4, 23, 24, 45, 46, 48, 50], "object_names": ["shelf", "box", "box", "case", "case", "case", "case"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 7 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [4, 23, 24, 45, 46, 48, 50], "input_bboxes": [[-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["All kinds of <object_8> can be stored in <box_23>."], "object_ids": [13, 15, 19, 25, 26, 28, 30, 34, 35, 44, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 59], "object_names": ["object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 17 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [13, 15, 19, 25, 26, 28, 30, 34, 35, 44, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["This area serves as a versatile study space, equipped with a workstation and storage solutions, and is connected to other parts of the space through a staircase."], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "object_names": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the location and function description of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_0"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The study area is a medium-sized rectangular space with enough room to accommodate a large desk, several chairs, and a shelving unit. While specific dimensions are not provided, the area comfortably allows for essential furniture without feeling cramped."], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "object_names": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the space layout and dimensions of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_1"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The room has window, providing plenty of natural light. The walls are sturdy, suitable for placing shelves and hanging rails. The floor is solid, possibly made of wood or other hard materials, capable of supporting furniture and pedestrian traffic. The ceiling has an industrial aesthetic, with visible structural elements, and sufficient height that doesn't make the space feel cramped."], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "object_names": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the doors, windows, walls, floors and ceilings of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_2"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["This area contains minimal soft furnishings, emphasizing functionality, and exuding an industrial chic style. Decorative details include placing storage boxes on the shelves, and personal items such as bottle and cup on the table and bench, adding a homely feel."], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "object_names": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the soft fitting elements and decorative details of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_3"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The lighting design includes natural light from the windows and artificial light from overhead fixtures. Adjustable desk lamps provide additional focused task lighting."], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "object_names": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the lighting design of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_4"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The color scheme features neutral tones, including white, grey, and natural wood finishes, complementing the modern industrial theme. The minimalist approach avoids overstimulation and promotes a focused work environment."], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "object_names": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the color matching and style theme of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_5"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["This area's unique features include the juxtaposition of modern furniture with the rustic industrial style of the architecture, such as bare brick walls and arched windows, providing personality and depth to the study area."], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "object_names": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the special features of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 8, 9, 11, 12, 13, 15, 17, 18, 19, 20, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 48, 49, 50, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59], "input_bboxes": [[-1.0122929208618545, 0.8673264173745203, 1.9505519269802034, 3.9636228133537754, 1.0532552777249302, 3.792430780391536, 0.34973981242850444, -7.196821286303676e-17, -4.654972673719043e-16], [-2.2523613846588137, 0.6609350211715697, 1.2673816726994513, 0.623842, 2.52232, 2.59686, 2.9130006475419172, -1.5707963267948966, -2.1920868361882078], [-0.8873973846588135, 0.60269502117157, 1.8845216726994514, 3.30092, 0.335548, 3.70798, 0.3926985033454364, 9.231165294882605e-17, 6.168071314384912e-17], [-3.6460213846588134, -1.2230444546312678, 1.4645716726994515, 0.1799268, 0.515784, 0.5547490483943249, -2.0344439357957027, 1.5707963267948966, -1.1071487177940904], [-3.6375113846588136, -0.9833549788284301, 1.8902016726994515, 0.1931042, 0.891974, 1.434006, 3.1415926535897927, 1.2246466797550471e-16, -3.1415926325163688], [-2.4628113705127204, -0.9986349788284303, 3.2272916726994514, 0.21600397170781355, 2.07854, 1.237108, -1.094764425253763e-47, 4.930380657631324e-32, 4.4408920985006247e-16], [-0.08146204531432578, 0.371251874601182, 0.9874706726994514, 0.19652444292132498, 0.558688, 0.398964, -2.811968268141269, -7.21627446821917e-17, 6.433310921901689e-16], [-0.5658793846588134, -0.3760507466900219, 1.8081716726994512, 3.3134915357231836, 5.95348, 3.57642, 1.5707963267948974, -2.22044604925032e-16, -8.635508522760762e-16], [-2.965019628125847, -0.1892085297452539, 1.0645716726994514, 0.3972222315749265, 0.41438803241074407, 0.381654, 0.0040732247901765625, 3.1632127985115703e-16, 1.1813509479003412e-16], [-0.9062743846588135, -0.09673780956247588, 0.5045376726994515, 0.701036, 0.627770338531909, 0.9929, -4.440892194923865e-16, -4.440892051708224e-16, -2.1073424449902234e-08], [0.7272186153411866, -1.9338649788284301, 3.9330616726994516, 0.201716, 0.256104, 0.32411, -1.5707963267948961, -1.5700924586837754e-16, 4.236230052406948e-32], [-3.273821311522757, -1.0674743244788263, 0.9414381951143632, 0.1569542586640223, 0.18368469130079243, 0.1494989551701765, -4.440892098500626e-16, -2.7369110631344083e-47, 1.232595164407831e-31], [-3.0720419441410867, -0.8206649801526665, 0.43407611149924097, 0.9391648810354535, 2.0741113838993672, 0.8622008775995791, 5.551115123125783e-16, 3.140184917367553e-16, 2.2204460492503123e-16], [-3.1273282558339854, -0.6468294200398005, 1.0029316726994515, 0.4471170677023459, 0.4249635194191743, 0.264896, -0.05212664904564557, 2.311036435968643e-16, 9.066898111617377e-17], [-3.0441228851461064, -1.827895845929297, 0.34178474228272476, 0.8076416149377988, 0.37568203917789494, 0.653710148919391, 5.551115123125783e-16, -7.503411606360618e-24, -2.1073424893991444e-08], [-2.9545707622438493, -1.5517149788284303, 1.1177243964676733, 0.40236868521866365, 0.579462, 0.496341447536444, 1.232595164407831e-32, 1.570092458683775e-16, -1.5700924586837752e-16], [0.050062874675935544, -0.20880497882843008, 0.8559216726994514, 0.15329928133050202, 0.1449878, 0.195969, -3.1415926535897927, -5.770133065931889e-32, -1.5700924586837754e-16], [-0.06979156652786231, -0.8221208199584017, 0.8323656726994515, 0.16213255157728476, 0.1405126115204174, 0.1557234, 3.0132694259039994, -2.8302124471248863e-16, -2.604042909983118e-16], [-0.19690879672609946, 0.03008751150282815, 0.3995053159345062, 0.8617531520880879, 2.0228919994819954, 0.7441455855678916, 3.0979594222899354, -2.3186538822733104e-16, -8.870287460156359e-17], [0.0959646153411865, 0.17857502117156976, 0.8074486726994514, 0.0620722, 0.046567, 0.0734276, -2.777255337950229, -9.052542589931718e-17, -6.427362530482896e-17], [0.2593176153411864, 0.03656594160599173, 0.41145967269945144, 0.645332, 0.5826287686913237, 0.774738, -3.1415926535897927, -1.570092458683774e-16, 1.5700924586837762e-16], [-2.874731269640656, -0.9685285546858914, 0.14736600479808548, 0.42687643526102026, 0.6083472149295892, 0.26447866419726807, -0.1312213036167082, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.4320281273276207, 0.6992018708375769, 0.17311067269945143, 0.32104699265568276, 0.36197841408762244, 0.315792, -1.3359870029750107, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.23422508709208148, 0.7382044665689107, 0.26874180242742984, 0.6354885098309198, 0.308616, 0.487100259455957, -2.7857438212588503, -3.386094981495479e-16, 1.669204111172951e-16], [-3.025176003515441, -1.4456757505365159, 0.35047114296220694, 0.747316, 0.40623157141736976, 0.6553155526981121, -0.05569858644090257, -8.873474679213058e-17, -6.672403132166688e-17], [-2.980013940957728, -0.15170755847574735, 0.370133107195951, 0.7235760528658501, 0.5406685767809812, 0.7321034389446334, -0.004423388456872371, -3.097709282003944e-16, -1.4801650123673715e-16], [-0.4293517149560311, -0.5053360335883875, 0.7672598770410495, 0.35393333338256217, 0.7158977520350188, 0.036049045890435526, -3.1271616744748787, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.2721703049957573, 0.019617370362236142, 0.7783089900666161, 0.156466635141747, 0.06823992725007023, 0.036682720054450765, 0.1643281574260158, 0.0, -0.0], [-0.1861258793623612, -0.46211216975915786, 0.81657770826254, 0.09847539111233777, 0.088421043102925, 0.09282246586214567, -2.8862715509233725, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.6955739767189795, 0.5996621723056255, 1.0466337502002716, 0.1736902251720162, 0.23052461680534242, 0.2576839327812195, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.3974428555258105, 0.7297592429074061, 1.0553948707429683, 0.20271986218539478, 0.21615470166066822, 0.29170422678194524, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1504990831061503, 0.42858547545577513, 1.7271554566090843, 0.23233234722647295, 0.512978656586387, 0.17040224049924285, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.1364265531474276, 0.4391133822184499, 1.3591939516293934, 0.2290873975758972, 0.19469512839102301, 0.11093746612619089, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.5982101310982078, 0.689125390713249, 2.013206281227515, 0.1250223835135739, 0.4021376157275172, 0.2973818995394671, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4322687724448175, 0.6139616600168063, 0.9543304297243858, 0.12392100956110902, 0.08512674054725285, 0.11750478490313912, -1.0439933777169887, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.4352279933762544, 0.6100413843188075, 0.5911406398214103, 0.14857864720315994, 0.14812143739702538, 0.2781863814176614, -1.252144304260516, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.7229951150310363, 0.6224066330494407, 0.5086268607740929, 0.20732821833739878, 0.20743079209952417, 0.10629907767666771, -1.2345249823628897, 0.0, -0.0], [-2.703898979756226, 0.6133714861674271, 0.19849039104073807, 0.2555568057408694, 0.24831932233758033, 0.18836059351022735, -1.2228141407089979, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.8690674163057897, 0.8956780342682227, 0.6455309709511754, 0.21517893530366125, 0.37837389438313274, 0.1781090784576455, -1.223337547059585, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.9196217424501376, 0.8318156939186924, 0.20550240641843334, 0.12458379929699752, 0.3528816895617008, 0.35894430918978215, -1.2576327832407974, 0.0019386145189091127, 0.011373992071963768], [-1.5305979100813059, 1.0034479541580867, 1.1768398880958557, 0.1157927936144644, 0.1033727439386423, 0.06361258029937744, -1.426445979271504, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.3525341310227879, 1.101461641790728, 0.8138633007449991, 0.16914360773712148, 0.5359851519667151, 0.13026515556321275, -1.2396721747287858, 0.0, -0.0], [-1.815682347473808, 0.9175385953164165, 1.7689244735656637, 0.12548299693633097, 0.1720158636324307, 0.16331311280293567, -1.2345509140026665, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.336704469959014, 0.3989898112256379, 1.4691948659541392, 0.1712256161376669, 0.12303494301649263, 0.08522408011985111, -1.3100720547140738, 0.0, -0.0], [-3.255854127052569, 0.3993683726418842, 1.035179310257001, 0.22048150339573575, 0.2989807677718112, 0.1397158254846881, -1.2178203390026132, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["Sure! You can use the laptop conveniently."], "object_ids": ["17", "22"], "object_names": ["chair", "laptop"], "question": "What can I use to make it convenient if I sit on chair to work?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": ["17"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["You should use cup or bottle."], "object_ids": ["41", "42"], "object_names": ["cup", "bottle"], "question": "What should I use to drink water?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_8"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I can use adhesive tape to help him stand up."], "object_ids": ["43"], "object_names": ["adhesive tape"], "question": "How can I fix something if it's broken?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_9"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I can put all the case into a mess."], "object_ids": ["45"], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "How can I tidy up my things when I have a lot of them and they are very messy?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["Sitting on chair is more convenient for eating."], "object_ids": ["17"], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "How can I make my office more convenient?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I can check on the situation at home through the monitor."], "object_ids": ["12"], "object_names": ["monitor"], "question": "How can I check on the situation at home while I'm outside?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The ladder can be used to reach the high shelves for the book."], "object_ids": [16, 36], "object_names": ["ladder", "book"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_10"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["tall", "Large"], "object_ids": [16, 36], "object_names": ["ladder", "book"], "question": "In the dining region, this book and X have relationship in their function:The X can be used to reach the high shelves for the book. What is the size of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_12"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["rough"], "object_ids": [16, 36], "object_names": ["ladder", "book"], "question": "In the dining region, this book and X have relationship in their function:The X can be used to reach the high shelves for the book. What is the texture of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "input_bboxes": [[1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function0", "answers": ["The book can be used to reach the high shelves for the ladder."], "object_ids": [37, 16], "object_names": ["book", "ladder"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [37, 16], "input_bboxes": [[1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function0_11"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["book"], "object_ids": [37, 16], "object_names": ["book", "ladder"], "question": "In the dining region, this ladder and X have relationship in their function:The X can be used to reach the high shelves for the ladder. What is the type of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function1", "answers": ["rectangular"], "object_ids": [37, 16], "object_names": ["book", "ladder"], "question": "In the dining region, this ladder and X have relationship in their function:The X can be used to reach the high shelves for the ladder. What is the shape of X?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function1_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["These items are part of the reading corner setup, where the ladder provides access to the books, and the books provide intellectual enrichment or entertainment."], "object_ids": [16, 36, 37], "object_names": ["ladder", "book", "book"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 3 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 36, 37], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_6"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function2", "answers": ["These items may be part of a display or functional area, with steps allowing for closer inspection or interaction. This could be a decorative element or a tool."], "object_ids": [33, 38], "object_names": ["step", "object"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 2 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [33, 38], "input_bboxes": [[2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function2_7"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["This area appears to be a multi-functional study or work space located underneath the loft area, indicating that a ladder or stairs are used to access higher levels."], "object_ids": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "object_names": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the location and function description of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_13"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["This space, while compact, is well laid out, with a step leading up to a high platform that may indicate a loft area. There are no specific measurements, but it seems to be sufficient for individual study or work activities."], "object_ids": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "object_names": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the space layout and dimensions of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_14"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The area features a solid wall with a ladder against it. An exposed brick wall adds texture, and the high ceiling with industrial-style beams gives a sense of spaciousness. While the floor is not entirely visible, it appears to be concrete, fitting with the loft-style ambiance."], "object_ids": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "object_names": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the doors, windows, walls, floors and ceilings of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_15"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The soft furnishings are very minimalistic, focusing on practicality. Decorative details can be seen in the exposed brick walls and architectural elements."], "object_ids": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "object_names": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the soft fitting elements and decorative details of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_16"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The lighting is not directly visible in the provided visual, but the space seems well-lit, possibly with ambient lighting that highlights the walls and work areas."], "object_ids": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "object_names": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the lighting design of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_17"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["This area features a neutral color palette, drawing from the natural tones of the brick walls to provide a contrasting backdrop for modern minimalist furniture, suggesting an industrial or modern-rustic theme."], "object_ids": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "object_names": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the color matching and style theme of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_18"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["The room features the original texture of the walls and industrial elements, creating a unique character for the space. The clever use of vertical space through steps and ladders demonstrates thoughtful design."], "object_ids": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "object_names": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "question": "There is a study region in this room, these objects are in it. What is the special features of this region?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 33, 36, 37, 38], "input_bboxes": [[1.7165725071270928, 0.1871951770248142, 0.7199597694840382, 0.4771867649960585, 0.482587776092545, 1.3134387649960584, -1.4855334573543666, -1.5959455978986625e-16, -0.20883089364403964], [2.4451186153411864, 0.8638122436322158, 0.22252367269945145, 0.3557135550787085, 0.782786, 0.383436, -1.5707963267948952, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7306299230149675, 0.10061814243169331, 0.15733928658671503, 0.33204062327261724, 0.35679200044976755, 0.2387512560309434, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7216398614586905, 0.06825090748598366, 0.5731437243170522, 0.2697933956940711, 0.3141294701334645, 0.12254225352193697, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0], [1.7128529167767073, 0.16080509383404057, 1.044532223064603, 0.23292062952641535, 0.29550656399437714, 0.12058082517206349, -1.4559348433513093, 0.0, -0.0]], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_19"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I can put book on ladder so that I can reach it more easily."], "object_ids": ["36", "36", "16"], "object_names": ["book", "book", "ladder"], "question": "Where should I put book to make it more convenient to access?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": ["36"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_20"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I can get the book placed on the ladder."], "object_ids": ["33", "36", "16"], "object_names": ["step", "book", "ladder"], "question": "What can I get if I sit on step?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": ["33"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_21"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["Please provide context or more information for me to assist you with \"step\"."], "object_ids": ["33"], "object_names": ["step"], "question": "What places do I have to pass through if I want to go to sleep?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_22"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I'm sorry, but \"step\" is not a complete phrase. Can you please provide more context or a complete sentence for me to work with?"], "object_ids": ["16", "33"], "object_names": ["ladder", "step"], "question": "What would I be able to see if I sit on the ladder?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": ["16"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_23"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I am unable to translate \"step\" without additional context. Can you please provide more information or rephrase your request?"], "object_ids": ["33"], "object_names": ["step"], "question": "Where is the most convenient place for me to sit if I want to read?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": [], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_24"}, {"sub_class": "QA_Relation_Function3", "answers": ["I can put them on the ladder."], "object_ids": ["36", "37", "38", "16"], "object_names": ["book", "book", "object", "ladder"], "question": "Where should I place book, book, and object in order to access them simultaneously?", "scan_id": "1mp3d_0000_region7", "input_bboxes_id": ["36", "37", "38"], "input_bboxes": [], "output_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes": null, "ID": "QA_Relation_Function3_25"}]